<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<dialogue>
  <chapter level="1" init="intro" end-behaviour="none">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">Oh my god! Hi! I&apos;m so happy you decided to lend a hand around here. It&apos;s pretty lonely... er, let&apos;s jump right in!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">You&apos;re new to making talismans, right? Don&apos;t worry, I can tell you everything you need to know. It&apos;s not that difficult, trust me!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="right">See, these gems have innate magical properties. By linking circles together, the gems&apos;s magic can be stabalized and utilized for our own purposes. Really precise stuff, but you don&apos;t have to worry about that. Sorcerers far smarter than you and me have already figured this stuff out.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Now, give it a go. Click on a gem and you&apos;ll see a white circle. That&apos;s the gem&apos;s way of linking to other gems! Then, click on another gem attempt to complete the circuit. If exactly 4 gems are touching the circle, the circuit will be stabalized. Otherwise, it&apos;ll dissipate.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Here, give it a shot. Stabalize these 4 gems.</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="1" init="outro" end-behaviour="next-level">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">Look at you getting the hang of things! I&apos;m so proud of you!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Oooh, I&apos;m so excited. You&apos;re gonna be making cool stuff in no time! Only up!</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="2" init="intro" end-behaviour="none">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="right">Look at this gem! This is where things start getting interesting!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Certain gems contain more magical energy than other gems. This means one circle isn&apos;t enough to balance them out. This purple gem requires two circuits to balance it.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Notice when you attach one circuit to it, it will change color to blue. This means it&apos;s more stable than before, but it isn&apos;t quite happy! It needs another circuit!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">Go on! Give it a try!</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="2" init="outro" end-behaviour="next-level">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Isn&apos;t this just the coolest!!? These next couple should give you a pretty good grasp on sorcery; it&apos;ll be fun!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Oh, and as the talismans start to get more complicated, you might make a mistake or form a wrong circuit. No problem, just click a circle to undo it!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">You can also delete or redo the last circle you made by clicking the buttons on the top left of the talisman.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">Don&apos;t be afraid to make mistakes, that&apos;s how you learn!</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="8" init="intro" end-behavior="none">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">See, this isn&apos;t so hard! Let&apos;s kick this up a notch, yeah?</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="right">New gem! Look at that beauty. The cyan gem requires three connections. Good luck!</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="14" init="intro" end-behavior="none">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">You know what time it is? New gem time! Isn&apos;t this one pretty?</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">You probably already know what I&apos;m going to say, but I&apos;ll say it anyway.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="right">This baby right takes four circuits to be satisfied, kinda like how a circuit needs four gems to be satisfied. How ciclical...</line>
  </chapter>
  <chapter level="23" init="outro" end-behavior="none">
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Thank you so much! That&apos;s all the talismans I need for now. Maybe thanks to your help we&apos;ll get more commissions!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="smile">While we wait for more customer&apos;s to commission more talismans from us, it&apos;s always good to keep your skills sharp. You can practice on unlimited talismans.</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">These ones aren&apos;t as curated as the ones you&apos;ve been doing, so their quality can&apos;t be guarenteed. But you know what they say: quantity over quality! Or, well, something like that!</line>
    <line speaker="beth" mood="talk">Again, thanks so much, you&apos;ve helped my little shop so much! I&apos;m looking forward to working more with you in the future. Ta!</line>
  </chapter>
</dialogue>